let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Upon entering Teyvet, what did you fish out first?",
    answer: "Paimon",
    options: [
      "Emergency Food",
      "Fish",
      "Paimon",
      "Silly Mascot"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which continent did you first enter at the start of the game?",
    answer: "Mondstadt",
    options: [
      "Liyue",
      "Inazuma",
      "Mondstadt",
      "Fontaine"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who’s the oldest Archon?",
    answer: "Zhongli",
    options: [
      "Venti",
      "Zhongli",
      "Ei",
      "Nahida"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What reaction happens if you attack with Cryo and Pyro?",
    answer: "Melt",
    options: [
      "Freeze",
      "Thaw",
      "Melt",
      "Overload"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What reaction happens if you attack with Dendro and Hydro?",
    answer: "Bloom",
    options: [
      "Bloom",
      "Growth",
      "Burn",
      "Flourish"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who attacked and separated the travelers ?",
    answer: "Unknown God",
    options: [
      "Raiden Shogun ",
      "Unknown God",
      "Celestia",
      "The Archons"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Amongst the stellars, the bigger star symbolizes which twin?",
    answer: "Aether",
    options: [
      "Lumine",
      "Lyney",
      "Aether",
      "Mona"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the first enemy that you encounter in game?",
    answer: "Hydro Slime",
    options: [
      "Pyro Slime",
      "Hydro Slime",
      "Geo Slime",
      "Anemo Slime"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What reaction happens if you attack with Dendro and Pyro?",
    answer: "Burn",
    options: [
      "Bloom",
      "Growth",
      "Burn",
      "Flourish"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who’s Gnosis resembles a Queen Chesspiece? ",
    answer: "Venti",
    options: [
      "Venti",
      "Nahida",
      "Furina",
      "Ei"
    ]
  },
];




